At the Oscars / Grammys , Mason Jiang presented me with an award — while
scowling the entire time . The media reported that the award-winning actor Mason Jiang had
some beef with Anna Feng . That same night , Mason Jiang cornered me in
the dressing room . "I can't wait anymore . "
Mason Jiang and I met at
the Oscars / Grammys , became "enemies " at the Oscars / Grammys , and officially
got together — also at the Oscars / Grammys . The first time we crossed
paths at the awards show , I was just a rookie pop star invited to
perform . As a newcomer , I figured I should network , so I went
around scanning everyone’s QR codes — except Mason Jiang’s . The guy always looked like
he was sucking on a lemon . Even with my thick skin , I wasn’t
about to risk getting iced out . But as I walked past him , he
pulled out his phone and flashed his QR code at me . Nervously , I
added him — and then never messaged him . Later , I started noticing him
"coincidentally " showing up on my trips . Took me a while to realize : Oh
. He’s into me . Turns out his personality wasn’t as cold as his resting
face . He was sweet , romantic , and shamelessly direct . When I vacationed
in L.A. , he canceled his plans to play chauffeur and photographer for me .
I posted on social media craving a specific cake — the next day , he
had it flown in from another city . My favorite K-pop group had a sold-out
concert ? He scored bestie for me and my bestie . He spoiled me rotten
. Hard not to fall for that . When I asked why he liked me
, he deadpanned , "Your dance moves are hot . "
Who knew Mr. Stoic had
a secret freaky side ? I figured it was just a fling , so when
he asked me out , I said I needed time to think . Then came
the second Oscars / Grammys . That night , a bunch of hot young actors
asked for my WhatsApp . A few single guys were extra attentive — helping me
up the stairs , holding my dress , keeping me company . The internet lost
it . Twitter exploded with random ship names for me and every guy I breathed
near . And Mason Jiang ? He snapped . When he handed me my award