red the promise , then kissed me . It started soft — just a brush
of lips . When I parted mine , he deepened it , the heat building
until he abruptly pulled away , leaving me dazed . "Niannian ... " His voice was
rough , like he was holding back . "Cut ! " Mason detached immediately . "Perfect
! Didn’t know you had that in you , Bai’an ! " The director was thrilled
. One take . Mason stayed deadpan , like the guy who’d just kissed me
breathless was someone else . Meanwhile , I was the one struggling to separate him
from his role . His character reminded me of Mason when we first got together
— restrained but intense . "Ms. Feng , you’re not just a great singer —
your acting’s unreal . That shy , flustered vibe ? Chef’s kiss . " Ethan swooped
in with the flattery . I glanced at Mason . He quirked a brow ,
smirking , like Remember last night ? "Uh , Jiang’s a good scene partner ,
" I mumbled , then bolted to my trailer . Mason texted me : "Thank God
the director called cut . Almost lost control there . "
Me : "... "
Do your fans
know you’re secretly a horny menace ? That night , a forum post blew up
: "I work on a certain A-list drama set . "
"Today was their first kiss
scene . The ML barely has experience , but they nailed it in one take
. "
"Soon as they cut , he walked off . Zero interaction with the FL
— acted like she had the plague . "
"Poor pop princess . "
"Meanwhile , Ethan
and the FL were laughing nonstop . Total chemistry ! "
Only one project fit the
description . Netizens connected the dots fast . "If it’s that show , no surprise
. Dude avoids actresses like they’re poison . Pretty sure he’s gay . "
I showed
Mason the thread . "Hah ! They think you’re into guys ! "
He gave me
a look . "You tell me . "
"Before you , I also thought you were
celibate . You know how many fan edits pair you as the bottom ? "
Mason’s
face went green . "Guess I haven’t been thorough enough if you doubt me .
"
"No , no ! You’re , uh , very energetic . Peak masculinity ! " I
backpedaled fast . He seemed appeased — until he saw the comments shipping me and