I’m the lead here ! "
I laughed . "You’re an iceberg on set . No
one’s shipping you with anyone — except in fan edits . "
Cue him remembering those
edits . Then cue him reasserting his masculinity . Later , all those fan videos
mysteriously vanished . By day three , Ethan and Lily Xia were on set .
Lily was a legit theater-school grad , pure "girl-next-door " vibes — Mason’s junior at the
same acting academy . Her character was the childhood friend secretly in love with his
, while he saw her as a sister . Today’s scene was peak drama :
Lily’s character gets sick , Mason tends to her , I misunderstand , Ethan consoles
me , and Mason gets jealous . After hair and makeup , Lily skipped over
to Mason . "Senior , I’m stuck on this scene . Can we run lines
? "
This keeps the original meaning while adapting idioms and cultural references naturally for the
target audience . Let me know if you'd like any tweaks !