s face was pure thunder . The media ran wild with theories : Mason Jiang
, the classically trained actor , looks down on pop stars-turned-actresses like Anna Feng .
The awards only gave her Best Newcomer for clout , and forcing Mason to present
it pissed him off . No one knew the truth — that later , he
pinned me against a wall , kissed me like he was starving , and growled
, "You said you needed time . Well , I can’t wait anymore . "
I
thought , Hey , He’s hot . Why not give it a try ? So
we got together . Somehow , two years flew by . When I asked him
later why his confession was so shallow , he shrugged . "Guys , notice looks
first . What’s the big deal ? "
Hard to argue with that logic . Since
I was still climbing the ladder , we agreed to keep things low-key . Cue
the media spinning "Mason Jiang and Anna Feng : sworn rivals , can’t stand each
other . "
Then my agent , Dana , called — our new drama was officially
announced . I retweeted the promo post and tagged Mason . The comments exploded .
"Wow , money talks ! Two A-listers who ‘hate each other ’ suddenly co-starring ? "
"Mason
just won Best Actor , and now he’s stuck carrying this talentless hack ? "
"Rumor
has it Chloe Chen was originally cast . Anna Feng stole the role — y’all
know how . "
"Notice how Anna always lands big co-stars ? Wonder who’s backing her
. "
"Anna’s shows dominate ratings . She’s the top rising star — Mason’s fans need
to chill . "
"OMG , the visuals ! Cold , brooding king x fiery beauty
? YES . "
Eight out of ten comments trashed me . One was a timid
fan defense . The last ? Pure thirst over our looks . I kicked the
drama’s other lead — currently sprawled on my couch watching TV . "Your fans are
dragging me again . "
Mason grabbed my foot , rubbing his thumb along my ankle
like a creep . "Want me to clap back ? "
"No ! We’re ‘enemies ,
’ remember ? " Image first . "Use your fake account . " But I still wanted payback
. Laughing at my pettiness , he logged into the alt I made for him
and replied to a hate comment : "Random lurker here . Mason’s fans are unhinged