h whomever he wants . If y’all hate it so much , crowdfund a recast
. Maybe spend less time hating and more time studying . "
Within three minutes ,
my fans boosted it to the top comment . Instant satisfaction . The more his
fans raged , the harder he spoiled me . Nothing shut them up faster than
their idol publicly choosing me . Mason left early the next morning for a shoot
. I woke up at noon and checked Twitter . A trending tag : #
MasonJiangAirport He wore a basic tee and shorts , but his face ? Illegal .
Sharp jawline , deep-set eyes , towering height — he waved at fans ( which
he never does ), sending them into hysterics . Total heartbreaker . And I fell
for it . Who knew Mr. Aloof was secretly clingy and shameless ? "Wait …
are those teeth marks on Mason’s collarbone ? "
"OMG , I SEE IT ! That
wasn’t there before ! "
Fans with forensic-level zoom skills posted comparison shots . My face
burned . He’d be on set for a month — last night got … intense
. "Why does Mason seem weirdly happy today ? Still stone-faced , but he waved
? Suspicious . "
"Somebody had a very good night . "
Then , Chloe Chen tweeted
: "So tired . Don’t wanna get up . "
Since Mason was currently filming with
her , fans connected imaginary dots . "Am I the only one thinking this ‘exhaustion
’ matches the bite marks ? "
"Nope ! Mason’s always so cold — who knew he
was wild in private ? "
"Say what you will about Chloe , but she and
Mason do look good together . "
I saw red and replied , "Chloe’s radar for
clout is sharper than NASA’s . "
I forgot to switch accounts . Instantly , 99
+ notifications : "She’s not wrong , but Anna … babe , your main account
? !"
"LMAO , Anna Feng , unhinged queen . Spitting facts . "
Full-blown humiliation .
And just like that , Chloe and I were mortal enemies . After my agent
chewed me out , I posted : "Oops , gossipm forgot to switch accounts .
Sorry ! "
Mason’s studio quickly dropped his schedule , proving he and Chloe weren’t even
in the same state . Chloe backpedaled : "Just tired from work ! Don’t read
into it . "
I rolled my eyes . Sure , Jan . Then Mason