texted : "Damage controlled . "
Me : "Good job . You'll get your reward later
. "
Him , instantly : "What kind ? "
Before I could answer , Dana called
— Vanity Fair needed an interview last-minute . "So sudden ? I was prepping for
Mason’s drama . " His acting debut — no room for mistakes . "Just half a
day . They got ghosted by another actress . Since you’re in NYC , they
begged us . They’ve always supported you — hard to say no . "
My vacation
: over . Ignoring Mason’s rapid-fire texts ( "Schoolgirl outfit ? Fishnets ? ?"), I skimmed
the interview questions . The shoot went smoothly — we’d worked with them before .
That night , Vanity Fair dropped a gossipser clip . The interviewer asked : "You
once said you only date based on looks . Still true ? "
"Mostly , " I
laughed . "Looks are still key . But now I’d want someone who … sticks
around . Travels with me , grocery shops , cooks , watches bad movies .
Someone who always says goodnight , no matter where they are . "
I’d bullshitted this
question a million times before . But now ? I was just describing Mason .
The internet noticed . "LMAO . Anna stays loyal to her ‘hot or nothing ’ policy
. "
"Wait … she got specific . Those sound like real memories . Is she
dating someone ? "
"PSA : When celebs switch from generic ‘tall , funny ’ to hyper-detailed
scenarios ? They’re taken . "
Damn . The internet’s too smart . "Since everyone’s so
interested in An’an , let me hype up her new drama that’s about to air
! "
"To all the haters above : An’an has clarified multiple times that she’s single
. [Photo ] Stop making baseless assumptions ! "
Fans rallied to promote my upcoming drama
while reposting my past statements about being single , gradually steering the comments section back
on track . Reading their supportive messages , I felt a pang of guilt .
If my personal life ever blew up , they’d be so disappointed . Just then
, a text from Mason Jiang popped up : "Honored to be your ideal type
. Miss you . "
Ugh , so cringe ! Even though we’d only been apart
for a day , I kinda missed him too . So I booked a flight