od Studios for the next day — time to deliver that "reward " I promised him
. # ChloeChenMasonJiangKissingSceneleaked The moment I landed , I saw he’d trended again . Seriously
? I fly over to surprise him , and this is the welcome I get
? Excited , I clicked to admire the acting legend’s kissing scene . Turns out
it was just a peck on the lips . "That’s it ? That’s the big
deal ? I got all hyped for this ? "
"Next time , tag me only
if there’s tongue action . "
"Everyone knows Jiang’s kissing scenes are as underwhelming as his
acting — consistently mediocre . "
"The girl’s gossip bought the trending spot . Move along
, folks . "
Even netizens weren’t impressed . Disappointed , I closed Twitter and headed
to Mason’s hotel . "An’an , here’s the key to Mubai’s suite . He’s filming
late tonight , but let me know if you need anything . "
I’d secretly contacted
Mason’s agent beforehand , and he handed me the keycard at the hotel . "Thanks
, Chao-ge . Don’t tell him I’m here , okay ? " I mimed zipping my
lips . "Don’t worry — I’m a vault . " He mirrored the gesture and left
. After showering and changing in Mason’s room , I was about to nap when
his call came through . "Babe , why was your phone off earlier ? "
"Forgot
to charge it last night . Just plugged it in after waking up . "
"Lazy
girl , it’s past 1 PM . I’ve already shot three scenes . "
"Hey , vacations
are for sleeping in ! " And I skipped mine to see you ! "Did you
eat ? Want me to order you something ? "
"Yeah , Xiao Zhao brought me
food . " My assistant often delivered meals . "Good . Eat up — director’s calling
me . "
I lied about having an impromptu ad shoot later and told him not
to call . He agreed and hung up . If he video-called during one of
his 5-6 daily check-ins , my cover would’ve been blown . I woke up in
a dark room . My phone showed a flood of texts from Mason : "Chloe
Chen keeps NG-ing . Slowing us down — so annoying . "
"What ad are you
shooting ? "
"Busy , babe ? "
"Director’s fuming . Another late night . "
"Text me
when you’re free . "
I replied , "Anyone would think you’re a simp . "
He