sent a pouty emoji . Hungry at 10 PM , I raided his fridge . Mason
always stocked up to avoid takeout during shoots . I whipped up instant noodles with
eggs , ham , and greens . Just as I took my first bite ,
the door opened . Mason’s eyes lit up . "You’re here ? "
"Here to deliver
that ‘reward . ’" I winked . He shut the door , strode over , tilted
my chin up , and kissed me . "Hey — let me eat first .
Starving . " I stopped his wandering hands . He chuckled . "Just instant noodles ?
Want me to cook something else ? "
"I was craving it . You eaten ?
"
"On set . " He pulled up a chair . "When’d you arrive ? Why not
tell me ? "
"Got here when you called at noon . " I slurped noodles .
"Wouldn’t catch you cheating if I warned you . "
He snorted . "And did you
? "
"Yep . " I showed him the trending screenshot . "Cosy with your side chick
"Total frame job ! Work only — I barely touched her ! " He even
raised three fingers like a pledge . "Any NGs ? "
"Nope . One take .
"
"But your kissing scenes suck , and Chloe NGs constantly . Liar . " I fake-glared
. "Let me prove how ‘bad ’ I am . " Then he demonstrated . I never
finished those noodles . By midnight , he was still asking , "So ? How’s
my kissing now ? "
Talk about self-sabotage . The next morning , a new trend
exploded : # MysteryWomanSpendsNightInMasonJiangsRoom "The ‘untouchable ’ heartthrob finally falls ? "
"That silhouette looks like Chloe
Chen — they’re filming together ! "
"Chloe’s known for latching onto co-stars . Open your
eyes , people ! "
"@ MasonJiangStudio Y’all dead ? Debunk this ! "
"Clickbait accounts are
scraping the barrel now . "
The leaked CCTV clip only showed my figure , but
Chloe fueled rumors by posting an OOTD in similar clothes . Rolling my eyes ,
I commented anonymously : "Mystery girl’s taller than Chloe . Stop clout-chasing . "
Mason texted
that Chao-ge would move me to another hotel . My agent Dana called next :
"Don’t stress . The clip doesn’t ID you . "
"Thanks , Dana . " Both our
gossip had prepared for this — we’d been dating for two years . She reassured