arrived . "We’re negotiating with the hotel . For now , let’s relocate you .
"
"Planned response ? "
"Your face was hidden . We’ll say it was a new assistant
tidying his room . "
Smart — killed two birds with one stone . The new
hotel was farther but stricter . "Only guests with NDAs here . Celebs use it
for secret meetups . "
"Any chance of spotting other couples ? " My gossip radar pinged
. "Relax — we booked the whole place . "
Bummer . No gossip . Chao-ge
updated me : "The leakeder’s fired , and all footage is destroyed . "
After he
left , I checked Mason’s swift PR moves : @ MasonJiangStudio : "The woman in
the clip is staff prepping Mr. Jiang’s suite . She left promptly . Please refrain
from speculation . "
They included "staff " photos and room comparisons , then sued a few
gossip accounts . "Support justice ! Starts with one fake photo , then spins a
whole wild story out of thin air . Do they think spreading rumors is free
? "
"This generation of paparazzi is seriously incompetent . Posting a blurry , unrecognizable pic
and calling it a 'trending topic '? I could do that too . "
"Is my
brother your go-to clickbait now ? Every time a woman appears near him , you
jump to rumors ? "
"Got here too late — missed the rumor , only saw
the debunk . "
"Look how fast Jiang shut this down — he’s practically sprinting to
distance himself from Chloe Chen . Bet that stings for her ! "
The hired trolls
and big fan accounts jumped in to control the narrative , and soon , netizens
were back to bashing Chloe Chen . The topic eventually faded . That night ,
Mason Jiang came home looking exhausted . He hugged me for a bit , then
went straight to shower . "No filming tomorrow . Wanna go somewhere nearby ? " he
asked , stepping out refreshed , towel-drying his hair . "After today’s trending drama ?
Maybe lay low ? "
"Your choice : a day out or a day in bed
. " He raised an eyebrow , smirking . "We’re going out ! " No way I
was risking being unable to walk the next day . But that hypocrite still pinned
me to the couch without hesitation . The next day , sore and barely f