unctional , I let Mason drag me to a farm outside the city . It
was midsummer , and the fields were packed with sunflowers — a blazing yellow sea
stretching to the sky , vibrant under the sunlight . We rented a bike ,
and Mason pedaled us along the paths , stopping now and then for photos .
His photography skills were trash — my 5’6" frame looked 5’2" in his shots .
I roasted him endlessly . Since it was a weekday and remote , the place
was empty . We roamed freely , not even bothering with masks , the gossip
from yesterday long forgotten . We picked grapes , ate watermelon , and took tons
of pictures , killing the whole day before heading back to the hotel in the
afternoon . That night , I posted a few shots on Twitter , giving the
fans a little update . The response was all love . I stayed for ten
days . When he wasn’t filming , we snuck off to explore . When he
was on set , I studied scripts in the hotel , then picked his brain
about acting when he got back . Sure , he often "taught " me in very
hands-on ways , but I still learned enough to feel confident about my next project
. Once Mason’s shoot was wrapped , we flew back to New York separately to
prep for the new series . Soon , it was time for the premiere event
. The whole cast , crew , and press showed up . After the director
handed out the traditional red envelopes , Ethan Lee came over to greet me .
"Ms. Feng , my little sister’s a huge fan . Could I get an autograph
for her ? "
"Of course ! Thank her for me . "
Ethan was a rising
star from a few hit teen dramas — bright , clean-cut , the kind of
guy I’d have crushed on before Mason . No way I was saying no to
a handsome face . I grabbed a pen from my assistant and signed . He
grinned . "She’ll freak out . Bragging rights for days . "
He went on about
his sister’s fangirl antics , cracking me up . Then I felt a scorching glare
from behind me . Sure enough , someone was glaring daggers . Ethan tried saying
hi to him , but Mason barely acknowledged it . So petty . During the
group photo , Mason stood next to me — but with a solid