half-meter gap , painfully obvious in the crowded shot . We’d agreed to keep it
professional . That night , Mason slipped into my room . I was watching a
paparazzi clip — muffled audio of Ethan calling me "Ms. Feng , " then us laughing
together , looking cozy . Mason snatched my phone and scrolled through the comments :
"Older woman / younger guy ? I ship it ! "
"Wow , the drama hasn’t
even started , and I’m already stanning the FL and Ethan . "
"If he’s not
calling you ‘sis , ’ he’s plotting something . "
He scowled . "Netizens will ship anything
. "
"Guess I’m just that versatile . Their edits do look cute . " I grinned
, oblivious to the danger . Mason’s expression darkened . He started unbuttoning his shirt
, advancing on me . He spent half the night demanding answers : Who’s the
better match — him or the puppy-eyed rookie ? Lesson learned : Never praise another
man in front of a jealous guy . The consequences are brutal . At dawn
, Mason sneaked back to his room . I downed a coffee that morning —
no way was I surviving otherwise . On set , Ethan waved at me .
I gave a half-hearted nod , avoiding further chat . First scene of the day
? A kissing sequence . Our characters were newly together — building tension , then
pulling back . Before filming even started , the set was packed with crew and
cast . Everyone wanted to see this . Mason’s past kiss scenes were famously tame
. "Why’s everyone here ? Non-essential personnel , out ! " The director shooed the gawkers
away . "Bai’an , don’t stress . Kiss scenes are tough on day one .
Multiple takes are fine . " He patted Mason’s shoulder , clearly buying the "bad at
kissing " rumors . The director walked us through the scene , asking if we wanted
to rehearse . "No need , " Mason said flatly . "I don’t rehearse . "
Oh
, you’re such a faker . I rolled my eyes and went to my seat
. We sat close but didn’t speak . The awkwardness was palpable . "Action !
"
Mason slipped into character instantly , pulling me along . "Niannian , I’ll always be
here for you . "
As New Year’s fireworks lit the sky , his character whispe